{
    "id": "0bb4ee6fad0248c08764e49fb11bbe35",
    "title": "Fill in the blanks",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "a5b41ec0b9264f28be1a884deb34c6c8",
            "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I ..................... him yesterday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "did not meet",
                        "did not met",
                        "have not met"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She didn’t say …………………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "anything",
                        "nothing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Professionals ……………….. teachers and lawyers should have good communication skills.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "such like",
                        "such as",
                        "as"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The bird is …………….. the nest.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The doctor ……………… saw me in the afternoon was a middle aged person.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "whom",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She asked him why ………………… late.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "he was",
                        "was he"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Something ………………. to be done about it.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "should",
                        "ought",
                        "must"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She wasn’t ……………….. impressed with the results.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "quiet",
                        "quite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "This is the ………………. film I have ever seen.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "worse",
                        "worst"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I saw ………………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "nobody",
                        "anybody"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}